<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:base="en">
	<title>Maya&#39;s Daydreams</title>
	<subtitle>this is where i hang out on the internet</subtitle>
	<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self"/>
	<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/"/>
	<updated>2024-05-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
	<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/</id>
	<author>
		<name>Maya</name>
		<email>youremailaddress@example.com</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>i managed to add an image to my blog posts</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday7/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday7/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am embarassed by how long this took me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/img/apollo1.jpeg&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of May 2024, I will be participating in weblog posting month created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Apple Annie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of other participants, &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024/participators&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of my topic ideas and some rules I wrote for myself, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 7/31&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Marry Me Chicken and Job Applications</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday6/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-06T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday6/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Another short post today. I have been home alone all weekend and my husband came home from visiting his sister today! I spent a big chunk of my planned writing time making a dish called Marry Me Chicken. It turned out really good, I can&#39;t really tell you anything about any wedding results. I also found a job opening that I need to apply for tonight. So excuse my short post today. I hope you all had a nice Monday!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of May 2024, I will be participating in weblog posting month created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Apple Annie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of other participants, &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024/participators&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of my topic ideas and some rules I wrote for myself, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 6/31&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>My website is one month old!</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday5/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday5/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here is the to-do list that i set up in this blog... once I figured out how to post... Let&#39;s revist my list... which I am realizing that I totally coded in a weird way... and let&#39;s also make a new list&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h4&gt;Website To-Do List&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Figure out how to edit stylesheet &lt;/s&gt; &lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Grid on homepage? &lt;/s&gt; &lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Figure out how to edit the home page (lol) &lt;/s&gt; &lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Figure out how to add pages &lt;/s&gt;&lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Add a now page &lt;/s&gt; &lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Turn this list into a page / add changelog &lt;em&gt; have not started! &lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Figure out how to set up webmentions &lt;em&gt; still working on &lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Start planting digital garden seeds &lt;em&gt; started, but this will never be done &lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Link to neocities &lt;a href=&quot;https://da-greenhouse.neocities.org/&quot;&gt;greenhouse &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Join a webring? &lt;em&gt; done &lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back, I am honestly impressed with how far I got! There was quite the learning curve with learning how to launch a static website, but I feel really accomplished! Even if my page is kind of clunky... Here&#39;s an  updated to-do list for future me to work on. I am mainly focusing on posting month this month, but these are the ones that have been bugging me while i click around...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;website-to-do-list&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Website To Do List &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday5/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add a changelog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Figure out webmentions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;neocities page build-out&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;find a new heading font for my website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;figure out how to add images to blog posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;update the general fonts on my website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;more shrines!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;add a resources page (with a free notion template, my other love!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of May 2024, I will be participating in weblog posting month created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Apple Annie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of other participants, &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024/participators&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of my topic ideas and some rules I wrote for myself, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 5/31&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Four Months Into My No-Buy Year</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday4/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-04T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday4/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I still have not figured out why images aren&#39;t working in my blog posts, once I do, I will go back and include images from my trackers because I feel like they&#39;re mildly interesting! I am not a web developer, and I&#39;m learning as I&#39;m going on this website...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like having goals. I have been doing a no-buy / low-buy all year, and if I was going by my stated goal at the beginning of the year to &amp;quot;buy nothing for myself for an entire year,&amp;quot; and then to &amp;quot;buy a reasonable amount with these rules&amp;quot; when I realized that that wasn&#39;t possible. To failing at both for a time, to maybe having one bad day a week, to then having one bad weekend a month. I would say that I failed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;january&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;January &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday4/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In January I started tracking my no spend with a very simple &amp;quot;No Spend&amp;quot; check box for every day of the month. For the first few days, it was easy to not spend money because I was home and tired of getting things from the holidays. It was so easy that I decided to not track at all. Until I got a $2.50 coffee at the courthouse while I was a jury duty... and then it just opened the flood gates. I didn&#39;t want to go back and fill in those days in my tracker because I felt so ashamed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I figured that maybe having one box to check was too much pressure. My perfectionist tendencies were getting in my way. At the end of January, I started tracking my spending by category rather than just having one big No Spend box that I could fill in every day. Historically, my areas have been clothes, craft supplies, books, and eating out, so I went with those. Making this change was super helpful for me, and I felt like I had a little bit more information to help me strategise a little bit better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;february&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;February &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday4/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This new system made February feel so much easier. I bought one clothing item, got craft supplies once (after finishing a project). I let myself get lunch/food out by myself once per week and stuck to it. I said I could go to a coffee shop twice in the month, but I HAD to sit down and be in the coffee shop and make it an experience. That all went great! But there were still purchases I was making that didn&#39;t fit into these categories, so I added a &amp;quot;questionable&amp;quot; category. Those little questionable dots started to increase in frequency as the month went on... A lot of them were wordpress related if I remember correctly, so I&#39;m glad to have finally moved on!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;march&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;March &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday4/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel very dumb for not backing up my old blog posts from the wordpress days, because I chronicled my struggles through all of this past March. March was the month that I felt like completely giving up, I felt like I was back to my old spending habits, and that I should just accept that this is the way I am. The big killer in March was books and I felt so bad that I didn&#39;t even both tracking them. I was also making lots of questionable purchases, and I was back to binge eating again. :(&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking back through my spending history though, I was still miles away from my spending behaviors in November and December of last year, and breaking bad habits takes time. I also noticed that my craft supplies purchases were zero!!! So I don&#39;t see March as a total loss!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;april&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;April &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday4/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I decided to keep trying, I started April with slightly different rules, things like I can buy a book, but I have to finish one first. The first week of April was full of questionable puchases, two books, and I ate out a lot! But that number started to dwindle quite a bit, to my surprise, gradually and kind of naturally. It helped that I figured out some ways to get books for free and started decluttering more. I also got a little bit deeper into my EMDR therapy, where we have been working through my relationship with money and stuff. More on that later...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;looking-ahead-to-may&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Looking ahead to May! &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday4/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My tracker is very different this month. I took clothes off my list because I realized that they weren&#39;t a problem at all... and I added alcohol as a new habit that I want to kick. It&#39;s just been starting to make me feel sicker than I used to. I also took off craft supplies. Decluttering and downsizing has me realizing that I really need to finish the projects in my basket before starting anything new. I have also started this new YNAB system, so at the moment, I don&#39;t really have money allocated to buying things or eating out, because I have some more concrete goals that I&#39;m working towards. I am VERY curious to see how this month goes after April went so well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of May 2024, I will be participating in weblog posting month created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Apple Annie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of other participants, &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024/participators&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of my topic ideas and some rules I wrote for myself, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 4/31&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A Dumbass Tries to Learn to Budget</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday3/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-03T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday3/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Today&#39;s fixation is the You Need a Budget (YNAB) system. I have been working very hard to simplify my life lately. Saying that feels like an oxymoron, but it&#39;s true! It really is work when you&#39;re actually &amp;quot;working on yourself.&amp;quot; One thing that I have been starting to realize is that when I avoid things because they stress me out, they still are stressing me out. Out of sight, out of mind doesn&#39;t really work for me. Does it work for anyone? I have been trying several platforms over the last few months to track my spending and set a budget.
Google Sheets and Excel were great for tracking and making pretty charts... but manually inputting every thing thing I spent money on stressed me out, and I felt guilty for everything, even if it was &amp;quot;in the budget.&amp;quot; Everything always went over, or something came up that I couldn&#39;t anticipate and threw the whole thing off...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also tried out budgeting in Notion for a while, and I actually might keep including it in my little daily / weekly tracking database, just to see how my spending behaviors and how all the other things going on in my life may or may not be related. Like, &amp;quot;oh that week where I took on way too much at work was the one where I bought lunch out a lot!&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;I always seem to buy courses at the start of a new month because I&#39;m going to change my life and reinvent myself!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried tracking my spending in my planner and keeping an analog category tracker. This one has actually stuck for the last few months, but it mainly serves as a visual queue and I don&#39;t need to be buying anymore books this month, or that maybe I should FINISH a crochet project before ordering a bunch of yarn for a new one. I can&#39;t really plan ahead with it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, I tried Rocket Money. This was definitely an upgrade from Notion just for the fact alone that my transactions were automated. I also like the visuals of how much I spent from month to month as a benchmark if I&#39;m making progress in reducing spending. It&#39;s also nice having the reminders about subscriptions. I have cancelled SO many of them since starting to use this app... But I still felt like I can&#39;t really plan ahead / see a way out of my particular cycles that I don&#39;t want to get into here, but I needed help prioritizing I guess?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was how I came around to YNAB... It&#39;s been less than a week so maybe I&#39;ll come back with an update post on this topic if it stuck, but I feel like I found a nice balance with seeing what my expenses are, what I think I want to spend on the unpredicatables of life, and how much I want at certain points in the future for different things. I can go in more detail in the update post as I document my experience a little bit more, but for some reason planning based on the money you have instead of what you are going to make throughout the month is really helping me with those short-term decisions and seeing how they impact long-term ones. Once again, these were lightly edited, semi-stream of consciousness morning pages thoughts, so I am not 100% sure if they fully made sense.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;See you tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of May 2024, I will be participating in weblog posting month created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Apple Annie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of other participants, &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024/participators&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of my topic ideas and some rules I wrote for myself, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 3/31&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A Peek Into My Morning Pages</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday2/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-02T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday2/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This month I am cheating a little bit on my morning pages. I try to write 500 words every morning in StimuWrite every morning, just to get the juices flowing. I am not consistent at it at all. I blame the fact that I have been really struggling to wake up early every day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am using my little 500 words goal that I have carved out to write blog posts this month... if any one was wondering why I included that in my personal list of parameters for this month. That is my optional rule that is meant to stretch me a little bit. Plus just get me in the habit of sitting down to write /something/.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Similarly to my dream of running the Big Sur Marathon, I also really, really want to write a fantasy novel. I actually have most of the plot written out, it&#39;s been sitting in my documents folder for about 9 months now without any updates from me. I always have an excuse about why I can&#39;t work on it, I need to study for my FE exam, I&#39;m tired, I decided to run instead (lol), I could list a million and one reasons. I honestly kind of hate advice that you need to do things every day to be serious about them. The irony of choosing to do this daily challenege is not lost on me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually did something  similar with the last iteration of this blog when I was still using wordpress / bluehost (derrogatory) for hosting. I did manage to make a post every day, except for maybe one or two days. So I know that this is isn&#39;t that much of a stretch for me. I have always treated my blog as an outlet for me to store half-baked ideas, and think out loud to people. But consistency in other things? Not so much luck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The time that I stopped working on my writing project and when I stopped doing morning pages coincided. In fact, the novel idea was born out of an entry just like this one. Albeit, I was doing handwritten morning pages then... and also not posting them publically. Julia Cameron would probably be very disappointed in me if she happened to find my blog (I love your work if you&#39;re here!). I am trying to work with myself and where I&#39;m at in life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Right now I am prioritising sleep and healing from burnout. I am trying not to add too much to my plate while also trying to stay somewhat consistent in my hobbies. I am also mentally preparing for a big move and downsizing our apartment. Along with running in a race last weekend, we also drove to a completely different part of California to look at houses. We ended up finding a place, it&#39;s very cute. We will need to downsize by over 200 sq ft, so decluttering is also taking up quite a bit of time. I am also enjoying running and crocheting, and blogging. Where does novel writing fit in? At the moment, I don&#39;t know, but maybe we can figure it out together!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of May 2024, I will be participating in weblog posting month created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Apple Annie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of other participants, &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024/participators&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of my topic ideas and some rules I wrote for myself, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 2/31&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>A Love Letter to the Big Sur Marathon</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/bigsur2024/"/>
		<updated>2024-05-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/bigsur2024/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/Users/mayaprice/Documents/Projects/mayas-daydreams/content/blog/bigsur2024/pic1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;excuse the broken image, i seem to not know how to post images in my blog posts yet, will add soon! In the meantime, picture a big little lies cut scene&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Running is one of my great loves. I&#39;m not very good at it, and it&#39;s taken me a long time to be okay with that. I think that one of the big journeys that I have been on since turning 30 is learning to enjoy things in spite of being bad at most of my hobbies. I am not sure exactly where this idea came from, but it always felt like things weren&#39;t worth doing if I couldn&#39;t do it perfectly. Yes, I am a recovering perfectionist. Last weekend I participated in the Big Sur Marathon... not the full marathon... the 12k.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been dreaming of doing the &lt;em&gt;actual&lt;/em&gt; for many, many years. It&#39;s still a dream!! I even signed up for the full marathon twice and injured myself... twice. Both of those failures really crushed me. My relationship with running and myself were in a dark place for a while. All of the miles, hours of running, and running essays I read were worth nothing because I didn&#39;t make it to the start line.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Big Sur Marathon is... special. It&#39;s really not a good choice for people who are looking to run their first marathon. Although this year was not the usual course because a portion of Highway 1 washed out in a storm. It is also either one of the, or THE hilliest marathon in the country. Those heights pay off though because you&#39;re running along one of the most iconic roadways in the world. And because it&#39;s on Highway 1, which means they need to close the highway for race day means that there&#39;s a pretty strict time limit of 6 hours. There&#39;s something about the combination of the scenery, the physical challenge, and that ever present threat that the highway will one day completely fall into the ocean makes me really want to experience the full 26.2 mile distance on foot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now that I know where I&#39;m at with my running better now, I think that I could maybe make it to 6 hours on a perfectly flat course. Realizing I was going to fail this race not once, but twice really felt like I died trying. To my credit, I recovered and kept running, I set more realistic goals, and am keeping the marathon on my bucket list. I actually ran my first half marathon in March! So I would say that I&#39;m well on my way to making it to the start line again. I had the time of my life this weekend running along the highway for a bit and then through Point Lobos Reserve was a dream. Gorgeous. I went into Sunday just wanting to have a good time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&#39;m a little bit weirdly obsessed with this race, but it turns out that I&#39;m not alone in that. I feel like I got a taste of the experience that I was craving. The only sounds at one point were my footsteps and the waves hitting the rocks down below. It was beautiful and I felt strong. I had a plan for when I would eat my little snack, I knew exactly when I wanted to take a walking break. Much to my amazing luck that was also the point where the big 12k photo op was, so my pictures make it look like I just went on a nice seaside stroll, looking for mermaids.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of May 2024, I will be participating in weblog posting month created by &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Annie Greens&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of other participants, &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024/participators&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For a list of my topic ideas and some rules I wrote for myself, &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;go here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Post 1/31&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>It&#39;s Weblog Posting Month! + 31 Blog Post Ideas</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/weblogpomo2024/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-30T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/weblogpomo2024/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I recently set up my &lt;a href=&quot;https://mastodon.social/@mayasdaydreams&quot;&gt;Mastodon&lt;/a&gt; profile. I am dubious about it, but I did come across this hashtag: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mastodon.social/tags/weblogpomo2024&quot;&gt;#weblogpomo2024&lt;/a&gt;. Despite my better judgement, I want to go for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-is-weblogpomo&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;What is WeblogPoMo? &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Started by &lt;a href=&quot;https://weblog.anniegreens.lol/weblog-posting-month-2024&quot;&gt;Apple Annie&lt;/a&gt;, Weblog Posting Month (#WeblogPoMo2024) is a one-month blogging challenge to post daily between May 1st, 2024 and May 31st, 2024. Anyone with a personal blog should participate!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;da-rules-my-rules&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Da Rules (my rules) &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are the rules that I have set for myself&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post every day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am allowed to batch write posts ahead of time (I know myself, and I want to set myself up for success 😇)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;500 Word Minimum (arbitrarily) per post&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact with at least one other blog each day!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have fun and be creative 😚&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;31-topic-ideas-some-of-these-are-very-specific-but-feel-free-to-borrow-from-this-list&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;31 Topic Ideas (some of these are very specific, but feel free to borrow from this list) &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blogging and why I like blogging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My most recent trip&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More thoughts on decluttering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A rant about how my insurance seems to really want to keep me out of therapy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anxieties about moving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Book review(s)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recipes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fan girl about notion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write about the process of building the shrine section of my web page&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Document building my mermaid shrine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Taylor swift album review (at some point I want to go through all of them!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly general life updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A collection of interesting links&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An updated list of things I want to do to improve my blog&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reflect on my first month on the indie web&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a post about my cat (link to his shrine, does he have a shrine yet)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write a post about Porter (RIP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thoughts on no-buys and low-buys&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Publish more digital garden content (and be a little less of a perfectionist about it)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A post about my relationship with perfectionism&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mermaid shrine post&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MerMay art!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload a page from my physical journal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A post about my trip to the UK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An update on my Japanese-learning journey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upload a notion template for folks 💖&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How has trying to embrace slow / simple living been going for me?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What are some other things that I have been fixated on in the past?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How are my 30s going so far?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What have I learned about personal finance?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can’t believe I haven’t come to the end of this list without a post climate change-specific idea… so this is that post idea 🌏&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;it-s-also-mermay&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;It’s also MerMay &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s also MerMay which is an art challenge (think inktober) where you draw a mermaid theme piece of art every day. I don’t think that’s necessarily sustainable for me, but I’d love to mix some mermaid themed things that I have been working on throughout the month… maybe even get myself motivated to finally start working on my novel again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;why-am-i-doing-this&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Why Am I Doing This? &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been blogging on this page for about a month now, and I feel like the main thing I am missing is community. This seems like the perfect way to interact with other bloggers a little bit more! Also it was the motivation I needed to finally set up an RSS feed (easier than I thought it would be!!)!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;pomo-post-mortem&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;PoMo Post Mortem &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/weblogpomo2024/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2024 WeblogPoMo Final Post List&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/bigsur2024/&quot;&gt;A Love Letter to the Big Sur Marathon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday2/&quot;&gt;A Peek Into My Morning Pages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday3/&quot;&gt;A Dumbass Tries to Learn to Budget&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday4/&quot;&gt;Four Months Into My No-Buy Year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday5/&quot;&gt;My website is one month old!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday6/&quot;&gt;My website is one month old!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/pomoday7&quot;&gt;i managed to add an image to my blog posts, but...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>It&#39;s Been a Weird Week</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/been-a-weird-week/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-23T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/been-a-weird-week/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Happy belated Earth Day! It has been a weird week for me, and I feel like since that last time I sat down to do an update a lot of things in my life have already changed again. There are just some periods in life where things move fast I guess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;personal-updates&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Personal updates &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/been-a-weird-week/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One strange thing about being in the climate field that I still haven&#39;t quite gotten a grip on, is that Earth Day, Earth Week, and Earth Month are VERY busy. It&#39;s nice to take a beat to celebrate the planet with folks, but the rest of the work doesn&#39;t stop in the meantime! On top of that, I also found out that I basically need to start looking for a new job... which is depressing, but I&#39;m working through it...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been pouring more and more time into this page, making tiny tweaks, adding little pages that I haven&#39;t created links for yet... There may or may not be a chance to explore a certain shrine that I started in the music section of this post...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The only other thing that has been taking up quite a bit of my time &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/I-need-to-declutter/&quot;&gt;decluttering&lt;/a&gt; and unpacking (pun not intended) my relationship with &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/digital-garden/minimalism/&quot;&gt;minimalism&lt;/a&gt;. I have since done some trips to donation centers and little libraries, but I have also been going through my external harddrive. I have taken thousands of photos over the last few years, and these have also been some of the most transformative times of my life. I let go of a lot of photos, which surprised me. A lot of it was junk, photos of receipts or homework, screenshots of stupid tweets or painful conversations. Random stuff like that. But I also ended up going through pictures from trips and letting some of those go too. I am maybe halfway through everything, but I want to do a deeper dive and maybe host some pictures from my favorite trips here, so I&#39;ll come back to this. But going through these decluttering exercises have been really eye opening and cathartic. It feels like a tiny dose of healing, in a weird way. I promise I&#39;ll start blogging about more things than minimalism and decluttering soon, this is just the season of life that I&#39;m in at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;reading-enchantment-by-katherine-may&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Reading: Enchantment by Katherine May &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/been-a-weird-week/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This little book is full of so many little gems of wisdon and her writing inspires me to become a better writer. In honor of tonight&#39;s full moon, I will leave a snippet of a passage that I wrote down in my commonplace book:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a child, I would look out of the window on a nighttime drive and think the moon was following us. From my vantage point, she seemed to be chasing us along the sky, breathlessly trying to keep up. Later I learned that it was just because she was so big that it felt like she was everywhere, and that I was small with an outsize sense of my own importance. Still, I was left with the impression that the moon had a certain constancy. It seemed that she was attentive to my needs, concernedly checking in. Sometimes I felt like I needed her gaze.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;listening-the-tortured-poets-department&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Listening: The Tortured Poets Department &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/been-a-weird-week/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh boy, I am still unpacking this one. Taylor Swift album release nights have become a ritual for me at this point. And I even decided to start building my first &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/shrines/taylorswift/&quot;&gt;shrine&lt;/a&gt; for this site in the hours that I was waiting. It&#39;s definitely a work in progress, but I had so much fun learning more about css to make my own little swiftie corner of the internet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;goals-from-the-beginning-of-the-month&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Goals from the beginning of the month &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/been-a-weird-week/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In my &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/april-so-far24/&quot;&gt;first post&lt;/a&gt;, I made a list of goals. I thought it might be fun to revisit these before setting some new goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soak up that eclipse energy &lt;em&gt;I did indeed, and I made some new moon wishes too&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spend less money &lt;em&gt;I did indeed, I paid down some debt and owed on my taxes this year, so it doesn&#39;t feel like it... we also booked some travel so we made some big purchases too. But the general random spending on crap habit that I have been trying to kick is improving!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the numbers in Japanese &lt;em&gt;We&#39;re getting there, I haven&#39;t been practicing as much as I&#39;d like to with how nuts it has been. I have been watching lots of anime lol&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a better week at work &lt;em&gt;about that...&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do a new moon wishing ritual, and continue to follow the lunar cycle &lt;em&gt;forgot that i made a separate goal for new moon wishes along with enjoying the eclipse! but check! done! had a lovely time!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;goals-for-the-rest-of-the-month&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Goals for the rest of the month &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/been-a-weird-week/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full moon ritual! The fact that I am coming back on the full moon to do a life update is 100% coincidental&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply for 5 jobs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn those stinkin Japanese numbers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start going to the gym again&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Finish reading a book&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>My thoughts on minimalism</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/digital-garden/minimalism/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/digital-garden/minimalism/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;When I talk about minimalism, I am talking about the lifestyle, rather than the aesthetic. To me, it&#39;s a practice of owning only what is essential to you, and letting go of the rest. I also think that while related, minimalism and conscious consumerism are two different things.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>An Observation About Browsing Without The Algorithm</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/life-without-algoritms/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/life-without-algoritms/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I have been off of social media for a few months now. My accounts aren&#39;t completely gone, but I just don&#39;t visit the sites anymore. There was a time that having a presence on social media bothered me, but now it&#39;s just the incessant urge to scroll and keep up with what everyone I have ever had any brief interaction with (including if I just decided to follow them after bingeing Bridgerton). Simply logging off has relieved me of those awful feelings, and I didn&#39;t have to do anything that extreme (to me!!!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even if I have been off of social media, I still wanted to be able to enjoy the internet, and casually browse. That bumbling around trying to find a new home on the internet landed me here, for which I am very grateful. I almost forgot what it was like to organically find cool websites, or interesting people&#39;s work to admire. I feel like in a way I found a way to enjoy the internet again without algorithms (or at least minimally!).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One interesting observation I have made is that I spend more time thinking about whether or not I can trust the people behind the pages I find. Everyone I have come across seems to align in value with me, maybe that&#39;s just an aspect of the indie web, but I do have that moment of pause where I feel like I need to make sure. My hunch is that it&#39;s a reflex against being spoonfed content that is tailored to me, and suddenly being open to anyone&#39;s opinions. It&#39;s a nice feeling, just an observation...&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Recent Faves</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/recent-faves/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-13T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/recent-faves/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;iframe width=&quot;500&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4TffiAO-E_4?si=mTffkunRwOzb9gS0&quot; title=&quot;YouTube video player&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&quot; referrerpolicy=&quot;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Website To Dos</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/website-to-dos/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/website-to-dos/</id>
		<content type="html">  &lt;h4&gt;Website To-Do List&lt;/h4&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Figure out how to edit stylesheet &lt;/s&gt; &lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Grid on homepage? &lt;/s&gt; &lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Figure out how to edit the home page (lol) &lt;/s&gt; &lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Figure out how to add pages &lt;/s&gt;&lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; &lt;s&gt; ❑ Add a now page &lt;/s&gt; &lt;em&gt; completed 4/13/24 &lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Turn this list into a page / add changelog &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Figure out how to set up webmentions &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Start planting digital garden seeds&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Link to neocities &lt;a href=&quot;https://da-greenhouse.neocities.org/&quot;&gt;greenhouse &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt; ❑ Join a webring?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>I need to declutter.</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/I-need-to-declutter/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-12T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/I-need-to-declutter/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Last week we found out that we are moving this fall! I am super excited and nervous about it. Wondering if I can keep my job, what kind of place are we going to live in, am I going to like it, will the cat be happy? I think it will go great, plus we&#39;ll be a lot closer to the Sierras! But one thing that&#39;s been nagging me for a long time is the fact that I (and we) just have way too much crap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I definitely went on a retail therapy binge during the darkest times of the pandemic, and it took me a year or so after the worst of it had passed to realize that I didn&#39;t shake the habit. I am now faced with the daunting task of either packing and moving a bunch of stuff that I&#39;m not sure if I even want/need anymore, or just getting rid of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been curious about the idea of &lt;a href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/digital-garden/minimalism/&quot;&gt;minimalism&lt;/a&gt; for many years, but for whatever reason I haven&#39;t been able to commit to that lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was talking about the anxiety that the mess in my office has been giving me during therapy, and we decided on an action plan. I committed to just trying to spend 15 - 20 minutes a day decluttering. I am hoping that we&#39;ll be more or less ready to move by August. I was curious how much total time would I spend decluttering between now and August 1st, and it came out to 28 hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;28-hours&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;28 hours. &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/I-need-to-declutter/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If I needed one reason to distance myself from stuff, it&#39;s that. That doesn&#39;t even count the trips to donation and reuse centers, or trying to sell or give things away on Facebook, or on those odd days where I feel like decluttering for longer! This also doesn&#39;t count the time it takes to just clean our apartment in general... Is this really how I want to spend my precious time?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>April So Far</title>
		<link href="https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/april-so-far24/"/>
		<updated>2024-04-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
		<id>https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/april-so-far24/</id>
		<content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One week into April and I feel so much better than I did in March. Is March hard for other people, or am I just jinxing myself every year into having a bad month. Nevertheless, here&#39;s a little recap of my first week of April&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;personal-updates&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Personal updates &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/april-so-far24/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Work was super intense this week. By the end of the week I felt that good-old freeze response kick in as the sound of Teams chats and emails made me want to cry. It started with preparing for a stressful meeting where I proposed a project to my boss, then a public meeting that went a little sideways, too much work that I can fit into 8 hours, and a couple of passive aggressive emails from a coworker (as expected).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was also a week of great news too! My husband got into grad school!! Which we have been anxiously waiting to hear back about since last December. I am very proud of him and excited for our move. Thankfully we aren&#39;t moving far, and I should be able to keep my job! We both started to feel a little bit of anxiety now that reality is setting in and we&#39;ve got to start planning for a pretty big life change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also started learning Japanese this week! I feel like I already have a good amount of the hiragana alphabet down, and I was able to recognize a few vocab words in the Tokyo Vice dialog, which was exciting! I can&#39;t help but notice that people don&#39;t say &amp;quot;thank you&amp;quot; very much in that show, lol. We are hoping to do a trip to Japan this summer, which I am very excited to start planning for in earnest!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Putting time into this blog this weekend was such a nice escape from all that work stress. Especially because the nastiest email came in at around 4:45. It always feels so bad when you put a ton of work in all week, but there&#39;s always that one thing that you didn&#39;t get to. It just wasn&#39;t a priority for me this week, and I communicated that! Ugh, I&#39;m ranting about work again!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I feel like I should be thankful that work is always busy for me around this time of year, because the reason makes me feel a little proud. It&#39;s Earth Month! We joke on my team that every day is Earth Day for us because we manage a lot of climate adaptation projects at my workplace. Between organizing activities, giving talks, and keeping up with my daily work, it just turns into a bit of a flurry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am so excited about this blog though! It&#39;s only two days old and already feels like home.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;reading-the-garden-of-seven-twilights-by-miguel-de-palol&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Reading: The Garden of Seven Twilights by Miguel de Palol &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/april-so-far24/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Garden of Seven Twilights is such a cool book! I actually started it over this week because I got sidetracked and forgot what was happening. I picked it up in a bookstore in Ann Arbor when we visited for Thanksgiving last year. I was just drawn to the thickness of it and the semi-post-apocalyptic setting. I&#39;ll be sure to update as I get further in!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;listening-the-new-beyonce-duh&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Listening: The New Beyonce, duh! &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/april-so-far24/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am loving Cowboy Carter! My favorite song is bodyguard!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;goals-for-this-week&quot; tabindex=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Goals for this week &lt;a class=&quot;header-anchor&quot; href=&quot;https://mayasdaydreams.com/blog/april-so-far24/&quot;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soak up that eclipse energy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Spend less money&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn the numbers in Japanese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Have a better week at work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do a new moon wishing ritual, and continue to follow the lunar cycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</content>
	</entry>
</feed>
